又是两个六
Double sixes again.
不是吧
I don't believe it.
快给我钱 谢谢 还来吗?
Come on.Thank you very much,do you want another go?
来嘛 干吗
Come on,what?
你始终会赢的 我只是运气好一点而已
You're bound to win sooner or later.I just got a bit lucky,that's all.
好久没见过人出老千了
Been a long time since I've seen anyone work the tat.
- 不好意思 但是我认识你吗? - 我刚才一直在看你
- Sorry,mate,do I know you? - I was watching.
是吗
Pretty good.
我不就是运气好一点吗
Just got a bit lucky,that's all.
本作品由Norm HALFCD Team倾情奉献\N感谢原作提供资源.仅供学习交流.严禁用于商业行为\N请自觉于下载后24小时内删除!如果喜欢本片,请购买正版!
更多精彩 尽在www.NormTeam.com
压制:鬼谷子  字幕:鬼谷子\NCompression:GV-Sir  Subtitles:GV-Sir
飞天大盗 第2季第3集
S02E03 The Lesson
我是说 我看穿了你们的招了
All I'm saying is I'm wise to all your tricks now,that's all.
- 是吗? - 对啊 就是那样
- Is that right? - Yes,definitely.
- 这人很有眼光喔 - 他真看穿了
- The man's got 20-20 vision. - He's seen the light.
当你们走了我就好生意了
My profits went up when you lot went away.
我觉得你们这些年一直在骗我
I reckon you've been cheating me for years.
- Eddie 你怎么这么说 - 因为事实就是那样啊
- Eddie,how can you say that? - Because it's true.
我们叫的东西还没好啊?
Can we at least have our drinks?
我们等了至少20分钟了
I feel like we've been waiting here at least 20 minutes.
你们才刚过来啊
You've only just got here.
在我看来就像过20分钟了 你也觉得是吧 Mickey
Feels like 20 minutes to me.Does it not feel like 20 minutes to you,Mickey?
是的
It feels like 20 minutes to me.
- 可能他不想做我们生意罗 - 难怪他生意那么差
- Maybe the man doesn't want our money. - No wonder his profits are down.
有多差呢?没了20％的生意额了吧?
How much would you say they were down by,Eddie?As much as,say,20%?
- 20％?那够多了 - 我敢肯定是那么多了
- Twenty percent?That's a bit harsh. - You know what,I bet it is 20.
- 20％ - 对
- Twenty? - Yeah.
有那么多?
That much?
Eddie 说是20％就是20％罗
If Eddie says it's 20,then 20 it must be.
- 20％ 你干吗啊 - 好了
- Twenty percent,who'd have thought? - Yeah,well...
好了 你可要撑下去喔
no more,so you'd better get used to it.
- 5 10 找你 - 20
- Five,10....10 makes... - Twenty.
- 谢谢 Eddie - 谢谢你 亲爱的
- Thanks very much,Eddie. - Thanks,sweetheart.
- Edward. - Albert.
- 什么 - 开始了
- Well? - We're on.
Eddie 来杯咖啡 先记着帐
Do us a coffee,Eddie,stick it on the slate.
不能记帐 都给现金
No more slates,strictly cash.
- 又怎么了 - 被我们骗怕了
- Oh,not again. - The worm has finally turned.
Albert 说都弄好了 我们可以开始了
Albert says the mark's ready.We're good to go.
好的 Danny在哪?
Great.So where's Danny?
你是扒手?
You were a dip?
对阿 我是伦敦最好的扒手了
No,I was the best dip in London.
不会吧
You were the best dip,were you?
告诉你 我这样的高手可算是前无古人 后无来者
Telling you,mate,there's no one like me before or since.
- 不会吧 真那么牛啊? - 还不止
- Oh,yeah,your were that good? - I was better than that.
- 我很超厉害的 - 那 给我开开眼 见识见识?
- Brilliant. - Go on,then,let's have a look,show us.
- 你想看看? - 对阿
- You want me to show you? - Yeah.
我给你看看
I'll show you.
- 等一下 你的表呢? - 哇～
- First of all,hang on,you got the time? - Yep.
你 怎么 我不是一直...
Where did you....There wasn't....
厉害厉害 好了
That's good,that's good.All right,yeah.
- 好了 那现在谁会付帐呢 - 你什么时候弄的
- Anyway,so who's gonna get the bill? - When did....
我坐下的时候它还在我口袋里的
That was in me pocket.I was sat down on it.
别担心 别担心 我们还可以钱支票付帐 你要笔来签名吗?
Don't worry,mate,don't worry,we'll get a check.You got a pen?
听着 做我们这行 要事事小心
Listen,you gotta look after yourself,ain't you,in this game...
- 没人会帮得了你的 - 不用你说我都知道
- 'cause no one's gonna do nothing for you. - You don't have to tell me.
不用你说我都知道 我也摸爬滚打好几年了
You don't have to tell me,I was scraping around for years...
- 还没有人捉得了我 - 是嘛?
- before anyone would give me a shot. - Yeah?
过来
Come here.
好了 很高兴认识你
Top knowing you,top man,see you around.
我也是啊
Yeah,good seeing you.
你要去哪?
Listen,where you going?
- 我去坐的士 - 送我一程吧
- I'm just going off to find a cab. - Yeah,I'll come with you.
- 好吗? - 好的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
没问题
All right.
我跟你其实可以一起干
Listen,we could team up,me and you...
我们合作
you know,double bubble.
不要了 我是不做小打小闹的生意的
No,I don't work the short con anymore.
- 什么意思? - 我是吃惯大茶饭的
- Why not? - Moved on,didn't I?
- 什么 - 越做越大的大茶饭
- Yeah? - Bigger and better things.
- 例如呢? - 我去年就跟人家一起合伙骗钱
- Like what? - I joined up with a long con crew last year.
- 合伙了? - 对啊
- The long con? - Yep.
- 那很赚钱的吗? - 看情况拉
- That's big money,ain't it? - Can be.
- 让我也加入吧 - 不 对不起 我做不了主
- Can you get me in? - No,sorry,mate,it's not my call.
好了 人家带携了你
Right,so,someone gives you a leg up...
- 你反过来就不想外人来分一杯羹了? - 不是 不是那样 只是
- and then you shut the door behind you. - It's not like that,it's just...
- 他们还有很多人呢 我做不了主 - 你只是给人跑跑腿的吧?
- they're my crew that's all. - Just a gofer,is you?
不 不是 我也满重要的
No,I'm not.I'm an equal partner.
重要个屁 连这都做不了主
An equal partner who ain't got a say in nothing.
闭嘴
Shut up.
听我说 别在意 我要走了
Listen,forget it,I'm gonna go.
下次你到Neasden的话 给我打个电话
Next time you're in Neasden,give us a bell.
- 好的 Neasden? - 对啊 怎么了
- All right.Neasden? - Yeah?
- 那以前是我地头 - 是吗 现在可是我的罗
- That's my old manor. - Well,it's mine now.
Evelyn的咖啡屋还在吧
Evelyn's caf still there?
对阿 他那的汉堡难吃死了
Yeah,broke me tooth on one of her burgers last week.
那Blue Boy Pub呢?
What about the Blue Boy Pub?
还是那老样子 整天乌烟瘴气的 你过来的话 我请你喝酒
Yeah,still a dive.Come on round,I'll buy you a pint.
等一下 我们现在再喝一杯
No,wait.Let's have another drink.
- Danny还没出现? - 还不接电话
- Still no sign of Danny,then? - He's not answering his phone.
他会来的 我们开始吧
He'll be here.Time we got started.
Anthony Mgube 出生在尼日利亚 后来在瑞士定居
Anthony Mgube,born in Nigeria,resides in Switzerland.
他怎么看也不能算的上是个好人
Not a very nice man by any criteria you choose to apply.
当兵的时候就经常虐待犯人
His reputation in the army was for torturing prisoners.
后来退伍 涉足政坛
He left the army and joined the government...
后来因为被怀疑舞弊和亏空公款
then he fled to Switzerland...
逃到了瑞士
following allegations of embezzlement and fraud.
贩卖军火给东非的军方和雇佣兵
He sells arms to militia groups and mercenaries in East Africa.
一生有两大嗜好
He has two main passions in his life...
养马 他在Newmarket有个马厩...
his racing stables in Newmarket...
还有就是收集古董纸币
and his collection of antique banknotes.
怎么这么迟
All right.How's it hanging?
听着 我给你介绍我新认识的好朋友 Trevor....
Listen,I want you to all meet my new best friend,Trevor....
- Speed - Speed 这是Acie,Stash...
- Speed. - Speed.There's Acie,Stash...
- 还有Albert 这可是我们尊敬的Albert. - 好了
- Albert,that's the lovely Albert. - All right.
他就是我们尊敬的Albert.
No,he's the lovely Albert.
以前很有名气的 现在帮我们做策划 这是伟大的Mickey Bricks...
Legend,take note,this is the great Mickey Bricks...
骗术高手 最厉害的就是他了
con man extraordinaire,all round top....
- 别这样 Mickey - 过来跟你谈一下 Danny
- Don't do that,Mickey. - A word,please,Danny?
好的 你等我一下 Trev.我先跟他谈谈
All right,I'll be right back,Trev.I'll be back,Trev....
你他妈的发疯了啊?
What the bloody hell do you think you're playing at?
Trevor Speed 他跟我了
It's Trevor,isn't it?Trevor Speed,he's one of us.
你喝醉了
You're drunk.
- 我不就找了个帮手吗 没事的 - 你告诉过他什么了
- I've just had a couple,all right. - What have you told him?
没事的 听我说 他也是个骗子
It's okay,all right,listen,he's a grifter...
今天我见他在出老千
I caught him working the tat.
你不要带人来我们这
You do not bring people here.
如果有问题的话
If there's a problem....
没问题 没问题
There's no problem here,mate,no problem here.Okay.
有问题
Yes,there is a problem.
你干吗不听我说 Mickey
Why don't you just lighten up,Mickey?
听我说 他不是我随随便便找来的
Lighten up,will you?He's not just some muppet I found on the street.
- 他有心加入我们 - 我不那么认为
- I'm telling you,he's one of us. - I very much doubt that.
Mickey你让我难堪了 好了 是我叫他来的
Mickey,you're making me look very bad here,all right,I invited him.
别让我难堪
Please don't make me look very bad...
那我很难下台的 好了 我给他作担保 好了吧
'cause then I'll feel bad.All right,I'll vouch for him.Okay?
- 他底细我们都不知道 - 好了我会担保的
- We don't know anything about him. - Yeah,well,I do,all right.
你自己也说我们那单Gooby Dooby 的大买卖不够人手的
And you said yourself we needed somebody for the Gooby Dooby thing.
- 他叫Mgube - 管他什么了 反正缺人就是了 我给他担保好了
- Mgube. - And that as well.Look,I'll vouch for him.
就这样了 拜托 就这一次...
That's it,please,for once in your life...
相信我
trust me.
我不能 Danny.
No,Danny.
我们做事的人可要万事小心 我们得要弄清楚底细才能找人加入
It's all our necks on the line and I,for one,like to know the people I'm working with.
我们下次再谈
We'll do this another time.
- 对不起 - 我做什么了
- Sorry,man. - What did I do?
你能给我解释一下吗 我是超支了4英镑
Can you please explain the logic to me,of us going ?overdrawn...
你们负责通知我的却收我85英镑?
and you charging me 85 to tell me about it?
好了 现在我超支89英镑了
Well,now I'm 89 overdrawn.
谢谢 再见
Thank you.Goodbye.
- 什么事 - 那人真是个变态
- Problem? - Yeah,the man is a moron.
- 他不变态怎么去做银行? - 好了 这种小事别记在心上
- It's a prerequisite for his profession. - Come on,don't let it get to you.
不是小事啊 Mickey 我想你帮我去打他一顿呢
No,Mickey,I want you to go and beat him up for me.
- 你发脾气了? - 对啊
- Are we having a tantrum? - Yes.
他那样子弄得我紧张兮兮的
Do you know,he's starting to make me feel nervous.
很明显我们来了之后他的营业额就一直下降
Yeah,well,apparently his profits have gone down since we got back.
这世道什么都离不开钱啊
Everything's about money these days.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
别谈起Mgube那单买卖 迟点再说
Don't mention Mgube.We'll talk about it later.
Eddie 这是Trevor.
Eddie,this is Trevor.
对不起
Sorry.
对不起 就谈一下
Oh,sorry,look,one word,all right.
- 我们谈谈原则 - 原则?
- Principle. - Principle?
- 是啊 就谈原则 - 说吧
- Yeah,principle,okay. - Go on.
- 我也是你们的一份子吧? - 是的
- I'm an equal partner. - Yeah.
- 我说话也是算话的? - 当然
- I'm entitled to my say. - Absolutely.
- 我跟你们是一样重要的吧? - 一样重要
- I got an equal voice. - Same as everyone else.
我加入之前你们每个人都是认识的
Okay,you lot all knew each other before I come along,all right.
但是我就是刚加入的
To me,it's like I'm on the outside looking in.
- Danny. - 就是说
- Oh,Danny. - Yeah,it's like...
我当时也是个外人吧
the kid with the nose pressed up against the window.
还是在说原则问题吧?
So this,it's all a matter of principle,yeah?
是吧 Ash 不就是因为我能帮上忙吗?
That's it,Ash,principle.Yeah.
我说了我会担保他的 我想 我说话
I said I'd vouch for the bloke,didn't I?I mean,I think my word...
还是能当一回事的吧 如果你连我都不信
should be vouchable.And if it's not,then....
如果真是那样 我只能走了 咱们拆伙好了
I guess what I'm saying is,if it's not,then I'm gonna have to walk.
我说完了
There you go,I've said it now.
我的意思是
I mean,sometimes a bloke has to stand up for...
用人不疑 疑人不用吧
what he stands for.
他说的有道理 他毕竟是我们的拍档 怎么也该相信他
He has a point.A little trust goes a long way.
好的 但是我们还不清楚他底细
Yeah,but we don't know him.
我们当初要Danny来帮忙的时候 还不是不清楚他的底细?
Well,we didn't know Danny when we took him on.
好的
Okay.
Danny
Danny.
我们给他次机会
Okay,we're gonna give him a chance on this one job.
如果第一次就搞砸了 他就走人
The first time he screws up,he's out.
干杯 谢谢 你们不会后悔的
Cheers,thanks,you won't regret it.
我当时没给你面子 我不是故意的
I didn't mean what I said and sorry about burping in your face.
爱死你们了
Love you all.
- 那Mgube的买卖怎么下手? - 就投其所好好了
- So,how do we get to this Mgube? - His hobby.
他出名爱收集古董钞票
He has a world-renowned collection of rare banknotes.
他身家丰厚
Yeah,he looks like he's worth a few quid.
有人估算过 他身家大概有6亿美元
Last time,it was estimated at $60 million.
- 那有多少个0啊 - 好多个罗
- How many noughts is that,then? - Lots.
那要怎么下手
And the way in?
他很想要找的一张古钞
He's desperate to add one new note to his collection.
叫Yankee Green
Yankee Green known because...
怎会有这名字 因为是绿色的?
It's green?
是的 就是绿色的 那是以前用造钞工艺 现在已经失传了
Extremely so,yes.It was a new color process that did not catch on.
就因为这 它也身价百倍
But that in itself adds to its value.
那是一张面值$1,000的钞票 1866年发行
It's a $1,000 treasury note issued in 1866.
上面有George Gordon Meade将军的头像...
The head is of General George Gordon Meade...
联邦军队指挥官的葛底斯堡战役
Commander of the Union Forces at the Battle of Gettysburg.
那东西值多少钱?
How much is something like that worth,then?
全世界只剩两张了
Only two are known to still be in existence.
芝加哥联合银行买下了一张
One is owned by the Chicago Confederate Bank...
9年前买的 花了$200,000英镑
for which they paid $200,000 nine years ago.
我想Mgube一直也要买但是没买成吧
And I take it that Mgube has offered to buy it and been turned down?
他的确一直想买到它
Frequently,yes.
那我们有什么法子?
So,where do we come in?
还有第二张
Now,the second note....
很少人知道它在哪
Only a handful of people know its whereabouts.
总算被我找到了
Fortunately,I'm one of them.
给它作保险的那家公司的CEO是我的朋友
The CEO of the company that insures it is a friend of mine.
你朋友还真多
Everyone's a friend of yours,Albie.
它现在在Anne Foster手上
The owner of the note is Anne Foster.
是他第二任丈夫留给她的遗物
It is kept in her late husband's collection.
Mgube还不知道这事吗?
But Mgube doesn't know anything about her?
他只知道第二张钞票被私人收藏了
He knows the second note belongs to a private collector...
但他找不到那收藏家
he just hasn't been able to track it down.
就算他找到了Foster 她也说过她不想把钞票卖掉
Even if he did,she's made it clear that she will never sell it.
好的 那么有个百万富翁想找一样 东西而我们又知道那东西在哪
Okay,so we got a millionaire who wants something and we know where it is.
- 那 又怎样呢 - 我们去偷吧
- Now,what? - Can't we just nick it?
我们能伪造一张吗?
Can we forge the note?
能是能 但是Mgube可能连钞票的序列号都知道
Possible.But chances are Mgube knows the serial number.
我们得先去看看那张真的
We'll need to see the real one.
- 就是说? - 我们要找到Foster看看那张真的
- Which means? - Getting close enough to the original.
Foster?
Mrs.Foster?
没什么事 我们只是想对你在我们 公司投保的几件贵重物品
No,it's nothing serious,Mrs.Foster,we'd simply like to update our assessment...
更新一下评估
on some of the more valuable items that we insure.
- 不是已经更新过了吗 - 不
- My premiums are up to date,you know. - No.
手续上还要再确认一次
No,it's more a case of making sure...
确保那些物品的状况
that some of the items are in the same condition as...
还有担保的价值
when the insurance was taken out.
我83岁了
I'm 83,you know.
不是吧 你看上去就像75岁
I don't believe that.You don't look a day over 75.
你还要蛋糕吗?
Would you like another slice of cake?
不要了谢谢 好了 我们开始
Maybe later.Anyway,moving on.
首饰 好的 应该没问题
Right,jewelry,that should be fine.
- 这上面写你还有些旧钞 - 是我死了的丈夫的
- I see here you have some banknotes. - My late husband's.
知道了 好的
Right,okay.
对这些宝贝可要千万小心
Always a danger of damp with those.
我把它们放在个密室里了
They're in a sealed cabinet.
可以让我们看一下吗?
Do you mind if we have a look?
我们还要准备一点东西
There are a few more things we need for the Mgube con.
只是好像我们的流动资金不足
But it seems we're short of working capital.
于是我就想...
And then I thought to myself...
我能叫谁帮忙呢?
who do I know who could solve a problem like that?
- 我们还缺些什么 - 这是清单
- What do we need? - I've got a list.
行了 不算太多拉
Cor blimey,you don't want much,do you?
- 我留着吧 - 好的
- Leave it with me. - Okay.
你在我们酒店过得愉快吗 先生?
Was everything all right with your stay,sir?
请在这签名
If you'd just like to sign at the bottom for me.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好 来克星顿酒店
The Lexington.
这是信用卡中心
This is Credit Card Authorization.
你们遇到我们授权的问题吗?
I understand you've got an authorization problem.
- 没事啊 一切正常吧 - 是吗 刚刚我屏幕显示你们这有问题的喔
- Well,everything looks fine here. - It's just showed up on me screen.
- 我不知道什么回事 - 我来问你
- I don't know why that is. - I tell you what's happened.
- 你刚有进行信用卡交易吗? - 是的 有啊
- Did you just do a card transaction? - Yes,a credit card.
是吗 可能就是这桩交易出问题了
You did?Yeah,well,it may not have gone through.
你能提供那信用卡号 让我查一下吧
Do you wanna give me the card number so I can check it?
好的 号码是 4628
Sure,the number is 4628....
你好 我要用信用卡购物
Yeah,I'd like to make a credit card purchase,please.
好的
Okay.
镊子
Tweezers.
好
Yeah.
有什么问题吗?
Is something wrong?
可能没有吧
Probably not....
我想我们要照些照片
I think we may have to take some photographs...
用来更新我们的资料 可以吗?
just to update our files,if that's okay?
你们需要就照好了
You must do whatever you think best.
Yankee Green
Yankee Green.
- 你能仿造吗 - 那种纸可能难找一点
- Can you do it? - Paper might be difficult.
- 那水印呢? - 那个没问题
- What about the seal? - No,I can do that.
- 要给谁? - 给一个收藏家的
- Who does it have to pass? - A collector.
- 要送到实验室做测试吗? - 不 应该不用的
- Lab tests? - No,hopefully not.
- 能做好吗? - Stone先生 有钱可是能使鬼推磨啊
- Is it doable? - Everything's doable,Mr.Stone.
好的
- At a price. - Right.
现在先付一半 事成之后再付清
Half now,half when it's done.
但是我已经储钱进我的帐户了
But I've paid money into the account now,so...
你还不能扣清我的贷款额吗?
couldn't you just take off the charges?
为什么?因为客人是上帝啊
A reason?Well,how about customer service?
再说 这样做也合情合理啊
Or just plain,old-fashioned bloody courtesy?
我不是说骂你 我是想说
I am not swearing at you,I'm just trying to point out...
你真他妈的臭男人长着个猪脑子啊?
that you're an arrogant little man with a brain the size of a pea.
喂 喂
Hello?Hello?
- 他挂电话了 - 他真是没礼貌啊
- He hung up. - I can't think why.
好 这么不给我面子
Right,this means war.
不就是85英镑吗 这有点小题大做了吧
It's 85,my dear.Isn't war a little overzealous?
这是原则问题
It's the principle.
又是原则 现在都流行讲原则啊
Principle again.It seems to be the word of the moment.
- 穿上衣服 Albie. - 干什么?
- Get your coat,Albie. - Why?
我们要动手了
Because we are gonna get him.
- 整他? - 那个叫Hopkins的
- Get him? - Hopkins.
他见过我 所以我不能去 不过你可以帮我
Yep,he knows me but you can be my secret weapon.Come on.
对不起Reeves小姐 我们处理办法不复杂
Look,be that as it may,Mrs.Reeves,we have a very simple system here.
我简单给你说一下
Let me unscramble the intricacies of it for you.
你帐户有钱 你才能取钱出来
If you have money in your account,you can take it out.
- 但是你没有 - 孩子 走吧
- You haven't. - Come on,kids.
Hopkins?我叫Harrison Wyngate
Mr.Hopkins?Harrison Wyngate.
- 请进 - 谢谢
- Please. - Thank you.
- 让我来开 - 好的
- Let me. - Fine.
好的 下一步 要对付了Mgube
Okay,next step,Mgube.
我们跟他租车的公司有联络
We've got a contact in the limousine company he's using...
所以我们知道他今天下午会到Strand 的一家古董钞票商那去
so we know he's due to visit the banknote dealers in the Strand this afternoon.
- 我们能搞好的 对吧 Trev? - 对
- We can do that,can't we,Trev? - Yeah.
他今天对付那老太太的时候出色极了
He did really good today,Mick,with the old girl.
- 你跟人合伙骗过人吗? - 我只是听说过
- Have you ever worked on a long con? - I've read about it.
行了 好了 我去办这事 他给我做帮手得了
Yeah,well,I'll make the play,he'll just back me up.
那你还不如带上Ash
I'd rather you took Ash.
好的 Mick 你是老板 当然你说了算
All right,Mick,you're the boss,it's your call,but....
要不是有人教我 我也不会有今天啊
I mean,I wouldn't be sitting here,would I,if somebody hadn't taught me?
别把事搞砸了
Do not louse this up.
我们不会的
No,we won't.
要转帐是没问题的 你有在这开过户吗?
Setting up a transfer is no problem.Do you have an account here?
没有 外面的小姐给了我一张表格要我填
No,not yet but the young lady out there gave me the forms to fill out.
我们批准你的申请之后 就会把银行帐号给你
Once your application has been processed we can give you an account number...
到时你就可以转帐了
so you can arrange the transaction.
你打算要转帐多少钱呢?
Do you know how much you'll be transferring?
3百万
3 million,yes.
- 不好意思? - 这是启动基金
- Excuse me? - That's just the first installment.
- 启动基金? - 我所代表的公司
- First? - Yes,the company I represent...
将购入这边的地皮进行投资
has purchased some land nearby to develop.
我们要开户来进行资金调动
So we need a holding account,pay the construction staff,that sort of thing.
我想你们这样规模的银行能处理这种业务吧
Well,I'm assuming a branch this size can deal with that amount of money?
可以
Of course.
我就说了 有像你们这样的银行给我们做担保
I've always believed that having a strong relationship...
我们办起事来也会容易一点
with the branch you're dealing with makes life a lot easier.
再大一点规模的银行总部之类的话 手续就太麻烦了
Head offices can be so tedious.
对的
Quite.
说了这么多
Well,it'll be quite a coup for you,I guess.
这单生意能让你业绩增加不少的
I'm sure your superiors will be impressed.
手续一办妥 Wyngate先生...
Well,rest assured,Mr.Wyngate...
你就能享受我们银行的服务了
the bank and I will be at your complete disposal.
那就好
Lovely,brilliant.
好了我骗他入局了 你想要怎么做?
Well,now that I've got him,what shall we do with him?
我要想想
I'll think of something.
你当然要想了 我想你也会的
I'm sure you will,my dear,I'm sure you will.
- 我们到过不同的钞票商里去调查 - 你们是关税调查科?
- We're calling on all banknote dealers. - Customs and Excise?
是的 我们调查过你的帐户 你们当然是没什么问题的
Yeah,this is absolutely nothing to do with your business.
我们来也不是调查你们公司
We've checked your accounts.Everything seems fine.
我们来是想监视我们的调查对象
Just to let you know,we'll be here as part of our surveillance.
调查对象?
Surveillance?
对 有帮洗黑钱的团伙
Yeah,there's a money laundering gang,taking money out of the country...
喜欢把黑钱投资到古董硬币跟纸币上
by investing in rare coins and banknotes.
好了 你想我怎么做?
So,what do you want me to do?
没什么
Oh,nothing.No.
就当我们没来过调查
Just pretend we're not here and if anyone asks...
如果有人问起 就说我们是这的员工
then we're just members of staff.
但是我们不能让陌生人随便出入的
But I can't possibly have strangers wandering around the shop.
你既然不合作
Oh,well,should you decide not to help with our investigation...
是不是意味着 你这公司有些问题呢?
we would have to ask ourselves,why?
没有 当然没有 我会尽力协作你们的
No,of course,please.I'll help in any way I can.
好 那就好 谢谢
Well,that's super,that really is super,thank you.
你愿意先到后面的办公室去吗?
Perhaps you could wait in the back office?
几个小时应该就好了
Shouldn't take more than a couple of hours.
- 你好 - Danny.
- Hello. - Danny.
Mgube车到了
Mgube's car is just pulling up outside.
好的
Okay.
Harris先生 谢谢你的来电
Mr.Harris,thank you for calling back,sir.
我已经找到了收藏这张钞票的人
Yes,I have located the notes you asked for...
下午我就给你寄过去
and I will fax them over this afternoon.
没问题 我很乐意这样做
That's my pleasure,sir.That is not a problem,sir.
那张Yankee Green?
The Yankee Green?
是找到了
Have located it.
但是还没联络到收藏的人
Not managed to get hold of the owner yet,though.
当然的 我会第一时间给你电话的
Absolutely,sir.I'll let you know as soon as I know.
再见
Goodbye,sir.
请问一下 刚才你说的是Yankee Green吗?
Excuse me,did I hear you mention the Yankee Green?
- 什么? - 你谈电话的时候
- Sir? - You spoke about it on the telephone.
不好意思 先生 我不能透露其他客人的消息
I'm sorry,sir.I can't discuss orders from other clients.
你知道我是谁吗?
Do you know who I am?
我会买很多这里的收藏的
I'm here to purchase a large number of notes.
好的 那请你先看一下我们的产品目录吧
Well,maybe you'd like to have a little look at our catalogue?
不用了 我想你带它到我的住处去
No.I would like you to bring it to my apartment...
你一个小时后亲自带来
in person,in one hour.
我不知道能不能这样做
Not quite sure I'm gonna be able to do that.
你的收入是按提成的吧?
I take it you earn commission on your sales?
是的
Yes,I do.
我可要在你这花大钱的喔
I intend to spend many thousands.
一个小时后 带上目录 别迟到了
Bring your catalogue in one hour.Please do not be late.
你去哪了?
Where've you been?
- Mickey叫我帮他准备些东西 - 搞好了吗?
- Mickey gave me a shopping list. - Did you get what you need?
- 好 好的 - 好 我有另外一件事要你办
- Yeah,all done. - Good,I got another job for you.
不是吧 我也不知道自己这么重要
Cor blimey,I've never been so popular.
没 有件私事想你帮帮忙
Well,it's more of a personal favor.
说吧
Go on,then.
Stacie跟我都想你把这些凑合 起来做一份建筑规划
Stacie and I would like you to turn these into proper building plans.
用来干吗?
What for?
没什么拉 不过对Stacie可是很重要的事喔
Much as I'd love to tell you,it's more than my life is worth,dear boy.
好了 记得你要怎么做吗?
Right,you know what you're doing,yeah?
沉默就是金 我不该说话的时候就不说话
Silence is golden.Egg you on when I need to.
你一要走我就要拦住你
Get the hump when you move towards the door.
对了 就是那样
That's it,good luck.
你好
All right?How you doing?
Mgube先生在吗 他叫我们来的
Mr.Mgube in?Asked us to pop in.
- 什么回事 是刚才见到的同一个保镖吧 - 什么
- What's going on?Same bloke,ain't it? - What?
不知道是谁
Don't know who....
不
No.
他明天要签的话就给他钱
Offer him money as long as he agrees to sign by tomorrow.
如果他不签
If that doesn't work...
告诉小心他夫人和孩子的性命
then tell him I asked after his wife and children.
好的
Good.
你好
Hello.
我带目录来了 这是我助手James
I've brought the catalogue for you,sir.This is my assistant,James.
我对你的目录没兴趣
I am not interested in your catalogue,young man.
我想要的是Yankee Green
I want to talk about the Yankee Green.
我说过了 先生...
Did explain that,sir...
人家出什么价都不要紧
I will match whatever your other client is willing to pay.
不好意思 先生...
Yeah,I'm sorry,sir...
事成了我给你20万
And give you 20,000 for yourself.
我想我们不该再谈下去了
I really don't think we should be having this conversation,sir.
每人20万
Each.
对不起
I'm very sorry.
你说的是20万 每人吗?
You did say 20,000,each?
好了
At last.
终于肯了吧
Gentlemen in this country I can do business with.
好的
Okay.
那客人开价多少?
So,what is your other client's offer?
50万
500,000.
好的 把钞票带过来
Okay,bring me the note.
如果是真的 我给你钱
If it's genuine,I will pay you in cash.
- 这真是 - 你不是开玩笑吧
- This is... - Wait.You got to be kidding me.
我不相信啊
Oh,I can't believe it!
我们刚上去 他就中计了
Maybe we should have upped it.He said "yes" too easy.
你知道20万那有多少啊
Do you know how much money that is?
我知道 我们先回去 走
Yes,I do,boy.Come on,we gotta get back,let's go.
这边
This way.
你们今天早上去哪了?
Where did you two sneak off to earlier today?
Albie去银行见Hopkins了
Albie went to see Hopkins at the bank.
- 去干吗 - 那混蛋抢我85英镑呢
- To do what? - lf he can steal 85 off us...
我还付的起 那其他付不起的人呢?
how much is he taking off people who can't afford it?
分明是勒索嘛
It's extortion.
可能是吧 但是
Maybe,but...
你叫Albert出马有些太夸张了吧
isn't sending Albert a bit like using a sledgehammer to crack a walnut?
是要给他教训的
He needs to be taught a lesson.
对的 是该教训他一下
Right,I'm sure he does.
好了 他们回来了
Oh,here they are.
- 怎样 - 我出马会不成功吗?
- Well? - Am I the bollocks,or what?
厉害
Yes!
多少钱?
Price?
准备好了吗?
You ready for this?
- 你告诉他们 - 我来?
- You tell them. - Can I?
快告诉我们了
Someone bleeding tell us.
50万
Half a million.
不是吧
No.
那 之后要怎样?
So,what's next?
我一个小时前问过Ray了 他说钞票没问题
I spoke to Ray about an hour ago,the note's ready.
明天在Eddie的店里给我们
You can pick it up at Eddie's tomorrow morning.
好的
Great.
那个叫Stacie挺漂亮的 能上她吗?
Mate,that Stacie bird is a bit of all right.Is she up for it,or what?
想都别想 Trevor.
Don't even think about it,Trevor.
- 为什么不要 - 为什么不?
- Why not? - Why not?
因为她能把你当早餐的吃了
Because she's gonna eat you for breakfast...
连皮带骨都吃了 那可不是开玩笑的
she's gonna spit out the bones,it's gonna be very messy.
- 你上过她啊? - 试过拉
- Tried yourself,have you? - You could say that.
结果呢?
And?
我被她甩了好几巴掌
And I had more slaps than a Morris dancer's ankles.
- 可能是她不喜欢你这种类型的吧 - 难道她喜欢你这种的?
- Maybe you're not her type. - What,and you are?
说不定喔
Maybe.
警察 别动
Police.
- 很好笑 - 好了 Ash说你搞定了?
- Very funny. - All right,Ash says you're finished.
鬼斧神工
A flaming...
精雕细啄
work...
- 简直就是艺术品 - 是就最好了
- of art. - Pleased to hear it.
- 看上去满旧的 - 对啊 一般都弄成这样
- It looks really old,doesn't it? - Yeah,I think that is the general idea.
- 好了 钱呢? - 行 做的不错 Ray.
- Well? - Right.Nice one,Ray.
别一下花光了
Don't spend it all at once.
- 看上去真像 - 真是天才
- Looks good. - Genius.
- 你想能骗的了他吗? - 试试就知道了
- You think he'll go for it? - Only one way to find out.
谢谢 麻烦你了Mgube先生 再见
Thank you,sir.Thank you,Mr.Mgube.Bye-bye.
好了 我告诉他我找到卖家了
Okay,I told him I've located the seller.
我们谈好了价钱 我今晚会带过去的
Okay,we fixed the price.I'm gonna pick up the note tonight.
一切顺利的话 明天他就回瑞士
He's flying to Switzerland tomorrow.Everything's perfect.
我们应该没问题了
Okay,then we're all set.
- 你觉得怎么样? - 真是罪有应得啊
- What do you think? - It's evil.
谁叫他和他那么丁点的银行
Disproportionate to the 85...
还敢抢我85英镑
he and his stupid little bank stole from us?
- 对啊 - 好
- Yes. - Good.
这是零售区 电影区 娱乐区
This is the main retail area,cinema complex,theater district.
真大啊 政府批准动工了吗?
It's huge.Has planning been approved?
我们会给这里提供6000个工作机会
We're looking at 6,000 jobs.
政府那边其实也不会有什么问题的
The council has given us virtually carte blanche.
- 我想也是喔 - 6星期后土建就动工了
- I bet they have. - Construction begins in six weeks.
- 这阴影部分地方是什么 - 停车场
- What's the shaded area here? - Oh,car parking.
是在现在Portway Estate 那地方
That'll cover most of the current Portway Estate.
还剩下这么一块没买下来
And this is the only section that hasn't been acquired.
地方不大 却很重要 建成之后可是停车场的入口
Small but crucial.It will give us the best access to the car parks.
- 它现在是谁的? - 我不知道
- Who does it belong to? - I have no idea.
我们也不要管 停车场的承建已经让人家中标了
Fortunately,it's not our problem.We've put the car parking out to franchise.
不过不管是谁 这地到时可是很值钱的
But whoever owns it,they're about to be offered an awful lot of money.
你跟我说话?
You talking to me?
Neil Marchant 关税调查科
Neil Marchant,Customs and Excise.
Neil Marchant.
Neil Marchant 关税调查科
Neil Marchant,Customs and Excise.
我们在进行调查
Yeah,we're doing a bit of surveillance.
50万 50万
Half a million.
50万啊
你好 对 我是
Hello?Yeah,it is.
我是说啊 你老是没给过我机会
I mean,all I'm saying is you never give me a fair chance.
我老看不透你们的小把戏
It's all tricks and things I can't work out.
你觉得越来越蒙了?
So,you feel the odds are stacked against you?
对 我不是说我不要玩 但是 你看
Exactly,look,I don't mind joining in,but you've got Danny...
Danny 的找牌游戏我就没看懂
with his find- the-lady card thing,I can never find it.
那Ash又会弄些两面都是公的硬币
Then you got Ash with his double- headed coins.
对 就是两面都有图案的 两面公的
Yeah,double tails,'cause most people call heads.
就是了 我就说这个 这些小把戏
That's what I'm talking about,that,all that jiggery-pokery.
好 从此之后 你们都得像 常人一样付钱买东西
So,from now on,you pay for your drinks like normal people...
或者至少给我个公平的机会
or at least just give me a fair chance.
- 公平的机会 - 对啊
- A fair chance? - Yeah.
不是说因为你比我聪明啊 只是因为你骗我 才赢我啊
It's not that you're cleverer than me,it's just,you cheat.
好的 来 公平的机会
Okay,all right,a fair chance.
好的
Okay.
这有50块
There's 50.
你去钱柜拿50来
Now you take 50 from the till.
没事的 我的在这里 我不骗你
It's okay,look,there's mine on the bar.No cheating.
- 这一共多少 - 100
- How much is there? - 100.
我们出价竞投这100块 价高者得
Okay.So now we both bid for it and the highest bid takes it.
- 我们出价 - 对了
- We both bid? - You got it.
- 价高者得 - 价高者得 公平了吧
- Whoever bids most gets it? - The whole ?00.Fair enough for you?
好的 你先
Okay,you go first.
好的
Okay.
- 50 - 60
- 50. - 60.
好的 你赢了 给我60块 你拿这100块好了
Okay,you win.Give me 60 and the 100 is yours.
- 我赢了 - 当然
- I won,right? - Absolutely.
你会害我们坐牢的
You'll get us barred.
我也不想的 他送上门的
I cannot help myself.
- 好了 各位 - 你迟到了
- All right,chaps? - You're late.
对不起 老大 我有些事要办
Sorry,boss,I had a bit of business to take care of.We set?
好了 这是钞票
Yeah.Here's the note.
Ray说这只是看上去很像 化学测试是通不过的
Ray says it'll stand up to a visual but not if they run chemical tests.
一见到有试管之类的东西 马上说怀疑这钞票是假的
So the first sign of a test tube,complain about damaging the note...
- 马上走 - 知道了
- and get the hell out of there. - Got it.
今晚就要搞好 Mgube明天中午就要去瑞士
This has to be done tonight.Mgube flies back to Switzerland tomorrow afternoon.
好了 祝我们好运
Right.Wish us luck.
如果你是厉害的 你就不要我祝福你
If you're good enough,you won't need it.
等一下 我给你60了 你却只出了50喔
Hang on,if I gave you 60 and you only put 50 in...
我又被耍了一道
I must be a tenner down.
好了 我去跟他谈
It's all right,I'll toss him for it.
对了 跟上次一样
Right,same thing,yeah.
- 我来说 - 知道了
- I do all the talking,right? - Right.
记得Mickey说的 他们要是想要做化学测试
Like Mickey says,if he gets out some fancy testing kit...
- 我们马上想个借口走人 - 好的
- we make our excuses and we leave. - Right.
更重要的是 要表现得 紧张一点
The most important thing,all right,is to look a bit nervous...
好像我们不该去的
like we know we shouldn't be there.
他也知道我们真的这样做的话我们会失业的
He knows what we're doing could cost us our jobs.
就让他觉得他看穿了我们
Let's make him think he's doing all the running.
- 好的 - 你准备好了?
- Right. - You ready?
什么?
What's wrong?
- 不是吧 不见了 - 什么意思 不见了?
- Oh,no.It's gone. - What do you mean,it's gone?
我一定是把它落在酒吧了
I must have left it in the bar.
没 当时你就放进口袋了
No,you didn't leave it in the bar,you put it in your pocket.
- 我肯定掉了 - 没 你没掉 找一找
- I must have dropped it. - No,you didn't drop it,have a look.
不是吧 明明放好了的
I don't believe it,I put it in me pocket.
我也不相信啊
I don't believe you.
好了 别慌
All right,don't panic.
想想 好了 我们往回走 找找看
Focus.Right,let's retrace our steps.
- 好的 找找 - 怎么会这样
- Well,look then. - I don't believe this.
好好找 别再说话
Just get looking and stop with your bloody whining.
等一下 不是吧?
Hold on.What?
- 我发誓我放我口袋了 - 他掉了?
- I put it in my pocket,I swear. - He's dropped it,ain't he?
在我们去的路上
He's dropped it somewhere between here and the apartment.
我们也找过了 但是没找到
We've retraced our steps,but someone's picked it up.
死蠢Danny 你说你会担保他的
Of all the stupid....Danny,you said you'd vouch for him.
对 我说过 Mickey 这是谁都可能犯的错啊
Yeah,all right,Mickey,it could happen to anyone.
又不见我犯 就他犯?
Only it didn't,did it?It happened to him.
我们再弄一张吧?
Can we get another one made?
来不及了 Mgube 明天就走
No,not in the time.Mgube's flying back tomorrow.
- 那玩完罗? - 对 没办法了
- So we're finished? - Yeah,afraid so.
你不知道 你刚浪费我们多少钱了吧
Do you have any idea how much money you've just cost us?
好了 我也浪费了啊
All right.I've lost out as well,you know.
你一分钱没用过
You didn't put any money in to set this up.
我们可是在这上面花了好几千的 还要等机会
Got half a million quid just sitting there,waiting to be picked up.
- 让他离开这里 - 等等
- Get him out of here. - Hold on.
听着 你还是走吧
Listen,maybe you'd better go.
- 这不全怪我啊 - 我说了 你走吧
- This ain't just down to me. - I said,"Get him out."
走就是了
Hey,just go.Come on.
- 走啊 - 走
- Just go. - Out,get out.
好的 我走
All right.I'm leaving.
走拉
Get out.
混人
Losers.
喂
Hey.
好了 放下牌一下 我的腿好痛啊
Okay,just put the cards down flat for a second.My leg.
没跟他们玩牌?
Not playing cards with the boys?
Albert出老千
No,Albert cheats.
- 对阿 - 满开心的 跟Trevor一起
- Yeah,he does. - It's funny,isn't it?With old Trevor.
- 什么意思 - 不久之前
- What do you mean? - Weren't that long ago...
- 我跟他其实也是一样 - 别乱说
- I weren't that much different from him. - Don't be ridiculous.
- 你跟他一点都不像 - 不 我只做小买卖
- You're nothing like him. - No,short con artist...
- 骗点小钱过活 - 不是那样的 Danny他很贱
- scratching a living. - No way,Danny.He's cheap.
什么东西都离不开钱
Everything's about the money.
所以他领略不了这游戏的美感
So he misses the beauty of the game.
美感?
The beauty?
你就是美的
You know,you're beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 我能问你些事吗 - 什么?
- Can I ask you something? - I suppose so.
你一直拒绝我
You keep knocking me back,yeah.
是因为 听我说 是因为
Now,is it because....No,listen,is it because....
是因为我们一起工作吗?
Is it because we work together...
- 还是因为你根本对我没兴趣 - 你说呢
- or is it because you don't fancy me? - What do you think?
我以前也是以为因为我们一起工作 后来我想
I used to think it was 'cause we worked together and then I got thinking...
可能是因为
maybe...
我不是你喜欢的类型
I'm just not your type.
你觉得我喜欢什么类型呢?
And what do you think my type is,then?
我不知道
I don't know.
像Mickey一类吧
Somebody more like Mickey.
像Mickey的 还是就是Mickey啊?
Like Mickey or Mickey specifically?
我怎么知道呢
Well,why don't you tell me?
- 你们两我都爱 - 我们两你都爱?
- I love you both. - You love us both?
我们两你都爱的话
Yeah,but loving us both...
女生不是只要爱一个的吗
that's just one of those girly things,isn't it...
有些时候你不想去爱人
when you don't want to shag someone...
但有不想伤害到他
but you don't want to hurt their feelings,either...
你就把他当成只是好朋友 并且你不想破坏这份友谊
so you pretend you're just good friends and you don't want to spoil it.
我也不是太懂女人
So,just so I'm absolutely crystal clear on this,yeah...
我跟你是没戏的罗?
a shag is definitely out of the question?
- 你不介意我问问吧 - 不介意 我还挺高兴你问的
- You don't mind me asking,though? - No,I'm flattered,Danny.
好了 谢谢你肯跟我谈
Thanks for our little chat and...
还没损我
no offense.
当然不会啦
None taken.
不是 交易还没完 只是他有些担心 没什么的
No,listen the deal's still on,it's just that he's got cold feet,that's all.
- 你有那张票子罗 - 有的
- You definitely have the note? - Yeah.
什么时候给我
When can I have it?
明天早上10点前给你
I can have the note to you by 10:00 tomorrow.
- 10点 - 你准备好钱了吧
- 10:00 is okay. - And you'll have the money ready?
这你就不用担心了
Do not worry,young man.
- 明早10点 - 好的
- Tomorrow at 10:00,then. - Good.
再见
Bye.
那班傻冒
Muppets.
- Foster女士 - 什么?
- Mrs.Foster. - Yes?
我能进来吗?
Can I come in?
事情是这样的 Foster女士...
The thing is,Mrs.Foster...
我们看那些照片的时候 发现
when we studied the photographs we've discovered...
- 那钞票有点破损了 - 破损
- that the note has been damaged. - Damaged?
那是不可避免的了 所以我们觉得出价购买了这张钞票
Irretrievably,I'm afraid.Which is why we've decided to pay out.
什么意思?我想我该给我孩子打个电话
I don't understand.Perhaps I should telephone my son.
不用拉
No,there's no need for that.
我来也是带钱给你
All I'm here for is to give you a little bit of money.
- 为什么 - 为了那张钞票啊
- What for? - For the damaged note.
对不起 我还是没搞懂
I'm sorry,I'm afraid I still don't quite understand.
听着
Listen...
你记得我们拍了些照片吧?
you remember,we came to do some photographs,on the note?
我们发现那钞票有破损了
Well,the note has been damaged,darling.
我们公司觉得你也会糊涂的
The company thought you might find this all confusing.
这是15万现金
150,000 in cash.
是作为赔偿的
It's a sort of down payment to make you feel a little bit better.
你要在这上面签字
I just need you to sign this.
- 我要用私章吗? - 不用了 就签个名就好了
- I need my spectacles. - No,it's all right,it's just one signature.
在这
Right there.
当然 我要把钞票带走喔
Of course,I will have to take the note back with me.
我得给Peter打个电话
I have to call Peter.
说到银行 钱啊 保险啊 我是一窍不通的
I don't understand when it comes to banks,money,and insurances.
我得跟我儿子说一声
I really would like to talk to my son.
我对你说的也不是很懂
I'm not quite sure that I understand what you mean.
你已经卖给我了
Well,you've already sold it to me,haven't you?
你不记得拉?全都合法的 钱在这
Don't you remember?All legal,money's there.
我没卖什么啊
I'm not selling anything.
Blimey 你真健忘了
Blimey,you're getting forgetful,aren't you,sweetheart?
我走了 不送
I'll see myself out.
等一下 我不知道我要不要这样
Please,I don't think I want to do this.
Mgube在等我
Mr.Mgube's expecting me.
Mgube先生
Mr.Mgube.
- 带来了? - 对
- You have it? - Yeah.
你准备好钱了?
Do you have the money?
说好的50万英镑
500,000,as agreed.
- 另外50万呢? - 你同事又没来
- And the extra 50,000? - Your colleague is no longer with you.
那我就连他那份也要了
Which means I get his share.
钞票呢
The note.
给他
Pay the man.
跟你做生意真是愉快
It's been a real pleasure doing business with you gents.
- 你们在干大买卖 - 我觉得
- Something's going on. - I reckon...
应该就是现在了
about now.
- 我能帮你吗? - 我找Foster女士
- Can I help you? - I'm here to see Mrs.Foster.
- 谁? - Foster女士 她住这的
- Who? - Mrs.Foster,she lives here.
- 不是啊 没这个人 - 那你是谁
- No,she doesn't. - So,who the hell are you?
我住这里的 这是我的房子啊
I live here,this is my house.
- 什么? - 我们刚放假回来
- What? - We've just come back off holiday.
- 怎么样 Betty? - 还是该叫你Foster女士?
- How'd we do,Betty? - Or should we call you Mrs.Foster?
15万
150,000.
- 不是吧 - 这么多
- You're joking. - No way.
我们想最多就2万 2万5
We only had him down for 20,000,25,000 tops.
看来这小家伙全付身家放进去了
Seems the little shit was holding out on you.
我们也猜想他会有些钱的
Well,that's what we thought he had stashed in the caravan,but....
他也没让我们失望
Seems he came into a small windfall.
喂?
Hello?
对了
Yeah,it is.
我们的银行经理
Our favorite bank manager...
买下了他的旅行车
must have bought his worthless caravan...
和他那块地
and even more worthless land for....
15万啊?
150,000 in cash.
我想问一下 停车场的土建工程谁中标了?
Yes,I'm trying to find out who's won the car parking franchise...
就是那个Portway Estate 公司的开发项目
for the new development on the Portway Estate?
什么没有?那个开发项目啊
What do you mean,"what development"?
给我转去 规划局
Let me talk to the Planning Officer.
教你一招
Here's the note.
最重要的是要做的好像有点紧张似的
The most important thing,all right,is to look a bit nervous...
就像我们知道我们不该去
like we know we shouldn't be there.
他也知道我们这样做会丢了工作的
He knows what we're doing could cost us our jobs.
就让他这样想吧
Let's make him think he's doing all the running.
- 好了 - 你准备好了?
- Right. - You ready?
有什么问题
What's wrong?
- 不是吧 不见了 - 什么意思 他不见了
- Oh,no.It's gone. - What do you mean,it's gone?
好了好了 对不起
Oh,yeah.All right.Sorry.
我真不相信你们不等我就开始了
I can't believe you started without me.
我能租一辆房车吗?
Yeah,can I hire a limousine?
我叫Mgube
In the name Mgube.
真经典
It's traditional.
是属于Nigerian的...
Yes,it's sort of Nigerian...
你知道的
you know,yeah.
12件白衬衫 16条衣领 还有些领带
Twelve white shirts,16 collar,and a dozen assorted ties.
打扮
Perks.
除了白的还是白的 觉得怎么样
It's white or white.What do you reckon?
- 我觉得 - 我也会选白的
- Well,I think.... - Yeah,I thought white myself.
- 白的? - 对啊
- White? - Yeah.
说好50万
500,000 as agreed.
你知道Stacie是怎么做的吗?
Did you hear about Stacie's little contribution?
- 我知道 - 厉害 我自己也要赞一下自己
- Oh,yeah. - Brilliant,even if I do say so myself.
- 你要我站哪? - 前面吧
- Where do you want me,Mick? - Out front.
看他来不来
I wish I could see his face.
- 有什么可以帮你? - 怎么回事?
- Can I help you,sir? - What's going on?
- 封了 - 为什么
- It's been closed down. - What for?
不知道
I don't know.
CID找到了一个犯罪团伙 可能是骗子吧
CID just dragged a gang out of there.Con men I reckon.
- 你跟这有关系吗? - 没有
- Do you have any business here,sir? - No.
那 走吧
Move along,then.
- Eddie 你好像看糊涂了 - 对啊 你们怎么就没糊涂
- Eddie,you look confused. - Well,wouldn't you be?
让我解析一下
Yeah,well,let me explain.
不 别告诉我 我不想知道
No!Don't tell me,'cause I don't even wanna know.
真不知道你们是什么想的
Wonder where that little weasel's sleeping tonight.
好了 我们至少没把他的车也骗走啊
Yeah,well,at least we let him keep his van.
对啊 我们不是不能做到喔
Yeah,we did.We should have had that as well.
- 他自己找来的 - 把我们骗子的名声都搞臭了
- He had it coming to him. - Giving honest con men a bad name.
你怎么找到他的?
Where did you find the little creep?
不是拉 应该算是他找我们的
Well,he found us,kind of.
我不明白
I don't get it.
我估计他以前就只会骗骗老人家罢了
I reckon he's been fleecing little old ladies his whole life.
- Rice先生在吗? - 那是我先生
- Good morning,darling.Mr.Rice? - That's my husband.
他在吗?有个包裹给他的
Is he in?I've got a parcel for him.
- 他去世了 - 对不起
- He passed away. - Oh,I'm sorry.
- 我能代领喔 - 货到付款 75英镑
- I can take it. - It's cash on delivery and it's 75.
那是什么啊?
But what is it?
我想这是你先生生前
I guess what I'm holding here was most likely the last thing...
最后订的一件东西吧
your husband ordered before he passed away.
- 好了 我拿回去好了 - 等一下 我去拿钱包
- Listen,don't you worry,I'll take it back. - No,wait.I'll get my purse.
好的
Okay.
但他选错了对象
But then he made a very big mistake.
他居然搞到我奶奶头上了
He picked on the wrong little old lady.
奶奶
Nan!
唉 亲爱的
Hello,darling.
我们把他骗倒了 搞定了
We got him.Yeah,we did.
告诉你 他再也不敢去搞你了 你可是我们的荣誉嘉宾啊
I tell you what,he's never gonna con you again and you're our guest of honor.
- 我没怎么出来玩 - 是吗?
- Oh,I don't get out much. - Don't you?
那个司机人很好的
The taxi driver was very nice.
是吧 你没跟他乱说什么吧?
Was he now,you weren't chatting him up,were you?
- Daniel! - 我就知道你爱那么干
- Oh,Daniel! - I know what you old girls are like.
好的了 你要什么 来杯香槟吧
All right,what do you fancy?A little glass of champagne?
香槟?那我会整晚都很high的
Champagne?Oh,I'll be up all night.
你会整晚都很high 不是因为香槟
You will be up all night...
因为你会跟你最喜爱的孙子跳舞
'cause you're gonna be dancing with your favorite grandson.
来吧 我们来跳
Let's have it,come on.
听着 Mickey 你能帮我把钱存到银行吗?
Listen,Mickey,can I pay the money into the bank?
- 所有? - 对啊
- All of it? - Yeah.
我就想看那Hopkins
I just want to watch Hopkins counting his money...
把自己的钱存入我们的帐户
into our account.
你可能有点变态 你得注意点
There is a very wicked streak in you,do you know that?
我要这样做才心理平衡啊
Well,there's nothing quite like getting even.
没事的
Nothing at all.
谢谢你Stacie.
Thanks,Stacie.
来干一杯吧 敬爷爷一杯吧 奶奶
How about a little toast,then?Here's to Granddad,Nan.
干杯
Cheers.
- 说真的 Eddie 你真厉害 - 我不要听
- Really,Eddie,you have been fantastic. - I'm not listening.
- 为什么 - 因为你会骗我钱的
- Why? - 'Cause you'll take money off me.
- 你怎么这样说 - 因为你的确会骗我的
- How can you say that? - Because you do.
Eddie
Eddie.
好的 我听你说 但我这次是不会再开钱箱的了
All right,I'll listen,but I'm not opening that till.
好的 那很公平啊 我给你露一手
Well,okay,yeah,fair enough.Hey,I've gotta show you this.
你猜我多久能喝完三大杯白兰地?
How long do you think it'll take me to drink three large brandies?
看你多渴罗
Depends how thirsty you were.
- 不要一秒 - 不可能
- Under a second. - No way.
那赌多少
Yeah,how much?
不 我说了 我怎么也不会再开那钱箱的了
No,I've told you,there's no way I'm opening that till.
好的 就玩玩
Okay,for fun,then.
- 玩玩 - 是的
- Fun? - Absolutely.
- 不赌钱? - 不赌
- No money? - No.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
斟酒吧
Set them up.
- 不用一秒? - 对 不用一秒
- Under a second? - Yep,under a second.
- 我计时 - 好 没问题
- I'll do the timing. - Yeah,agreed.
- 你说开始就开始 - 开始
- Say when. - Go.
停 你输了
Stop!You lose!
好咧
Yes!
你别再这样干拉
Will you stop doing that,please?
就是拉 跟人家一样付钱买单啊
Yeah,pay for your drinks like everyone else.
祝Eddie.
To Eddie.
干杯Eddie 谢谢
Cheers,Eddie,thank you!